#### Resume

My name is Gabriel de Rezende Gonçalves, Brazilian, I'm 21 years old, I live in Campinas/SP, computer technician, attending the seventh semester in Software Engineering at the Pontifical Catholic University of Campinas and intern in Software Engineering at Daitan Group.



#### Contact

Email: contato@gabireze.com.br

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/gabireze

Website: gabireze.com.br

GitHub: github.com/gabireze

# Experiences

Software Engineering Intern at Daitan Group

February 2021 - Current

Supervised monitoring of systems development; Supervised monitoring of reporting; Supervised monitoring in the maintenance of systems or programs; Participate in technical and behavioral training

**Software Engineering** at SuperOpa and OpaBox

June 2019 - January 2021

Fullstack development in Flutter and Javascript based on software componentization using microservices and scalable solutions for APIs, development of resources available from RESTful Web Services, use of Vue.js as a Javascript framework, Node.js as a server-side Javascript execution environment. Experience with Agile methodologies (SCRUM and Kanban), use of Git for version control, Slack for communication between collaborators, project management by Jira and Trello. Implementation of tests on APIs or Webservices using Postman,

used to the Serverless Architecture provided by AWS (S3, DynamoDB, CloudFront, API Gateway, CloudWatch, SQS).

### Academic education

## Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Campinas

Bachelor's Degree, Software Engineering

2019 - 2022

#### ETEC Bento Quirino

Integrated Technician to High School, IT

2016 - 2018

## Technical abilities

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Dart, C, Java, PHP
- React, Flutter, Vue.js, AngularJS, Bootstrap
- Node.js, Express.js, Serverless Framework
- MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL
- npm, Git, Swagger, Docker, Jira, Trello, Figma, Postman, Slack, SCRUM, Kanban
- Visual Studio Code, Android Studio, Linux, macOS, Windows
- Firebase, AWS, Amazon DynamoDB, AWS Lambda, S3, CloudFront, API Gateway, CloudWatch, SQS

## Interpersonal skills

- Creativity, Persuasion, Collaboration, Adaptability, Time Management
- Organization of groups, Negotiation of solutions, Empathy, Social sensitivity
- Emotional self-awareness, Emotional control, Self-motivation
- Recognition of emotions in other people, Skill in interpersonal relationships